Guide to the Warwick Baker O'Neill Records, 1931-2001 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Warwick Baker O'Neill records 1931-2001 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Warwick, Baker, O'Neill
94 linear feet Extent: 70,000 Items
Advertising agency founded in 1939 as Warwick and Legler; closed in 2001. The Warwick Baker O'Neill Records span the years 1939-2001 and include correspondence, proofs, clippings, research reports, financial records and other materials that document the agency's activities, particularly during the 1980s and 1990s. Formats include as-produced radio and television commercial scripts, 16mm films, audio cassettes and video cassettes. Clients represented include Bacardi, Bausch & Lomb (Curèl and other eye drops), Benjamin Moore paints, Burlington Industries, Coty (Emeraude, Stetson), Crafted with Pride (Made in the USA), Driver's Mart, East Coast Energy Council, Fruit of the Loom, Glenbrook (Midol), Heineken (including Amstel and Buckler), Lehn & Fink (Lysol, Resolve), Prodigy internet services, Reckitt & Colman (Easy Off oven cleaner, Rid-X), Schering-Plough (Lotrimin, Coricidin, Drixoral, Coppertone, St. Joseph's, Di-Gel), Seagram, U.S. Tobacco (Skoal, House of Windsor), and West Point Pepperell. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
RL.01346
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted.
Unpublished corporate documentation is closed to research for 15 years from the date of creation. Personnel records are closed until 2041.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Technical Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Warwick Baker O'Neill Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2001.
Historical Note
Enter Biographical and/or Historical Note
Chronology List
1939 Company founded as Warwick and Legler when Paul Warwick and Henry Legler leave Cecil, Warwick and Legler agency.
1941 Wins first major account, for Pabst Blue Ribbon beer.
1948 Selected to manage advertising for Harry S. Truman re-election campaign.
1957-1958 Involved in landmark intellectual property suit involving Schick and Benton & Bowles agency.
1959 Henry Legler retires.
1973 Renamed Warwick Welsh & Miller.
1974 Warwick International Partners formed to oversee European accounts.
1982 Renamed Warwick Advertising.
1989 Renamed Warwick Baker Fiore.
1996 Renamed Warwick Baker O'Neill.
2000 EBP Communications moves to acquire Warwick Baker O'Neill, which continues to operate under its own name.
2001 Warwick Baker O'Neill announces its closure in August.
Collection Overview
The Warwick Baker O'Neill Records span the years 1939-2001 and include correspondence, proofs, clippings, research reports, financial records and other materials that document the agency's activities, particularly during the 1980s and 1990s. Formats include as-produced radio and television commercial scripts, 16mm films, audiocassettes and videocassettes. Clients represented include Bacardi, Bausch & Lomb (Curèl and other eye drops), Benjamin Moore paints, Burlington Industries, Coty (Emeraude, Stetson), Crafted with Pride (Made in the USA), Driver's Mart, East Coast Energy Council, Fruit of the Loom, Glenbrook (Midol), Heineken (including Amstel and Buckler), Lehn & Fink (Lysol, Resolve), Prodigy internet services, Reckitt & Colman (Easy Off oven cleaner, Rid-X), Schering-Plough (Lotrimin, Coricidin, Drixoral, Coppertone, St. Joseph's, Di-Gel), Seagram, U.S. Tobacco (Skoal, House of Windsor), and West Point Pepperell.
Restrictions on Access: Unpublished corporate records are closed to researchers for 15 years from the date of creation. Personnel records are closed until 2041. Original audiovisual materials are closed until use copies can be produced. Restricted documentation is designated by an "R" in the container numbering (for example, Box R1).
Collection Arrangement
Arranged into six series: General and Administrative Files; Account Files, New Business Records; Proof Books and Creative Output; Large-Format Materials; and Audiovisual Materials.
Subject Headings
Legler, Henry; Warwick, Paul; Warwick Baker O'Neill; Bacardi Corporation (Puerto Rico); Bausch & Lomb, inc.; Benjamin Moore & Co; Burlington Industries, Inc.; Coty (Firm); Fruit of the Loom (Firm); Heineken & Co; Lehn & Fink; Prodigy (Firm); Reckitt & Colman; Schering-Plough Corporation; Seagram Company; West Point Pepperell (Firm); Advertising; Advertising -- History; Advertising -- United States -- History; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- History; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; 16mm; Audiocassettes; Proofs; Scripts; Videocassettes; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
Bates Worldwide, Inc. Records
Foote Cone & Belding Communications, Inc. Records
Henry Haberman Papers
J. Walter Thompson Company Account Files
J. Walter Thompson Company Anthony Viola Papers
J. Walter Thompson Company Corporation Vertical Files
J. Walter Thompson Company Domestic Advertisements
J. Walter Thompson Company Review Board Records
Lore Parker Papers
McCann-Erickson Audiovisual Materials
Roy Lightner Collection of Antique Advertisements
Detailed Description of Collection
- General and Administrative Files, 1938-2001 and undated, (23 boxes)
  Restrictions on access: Unpublished corporate documentation is closed to research for 15 years from the date of creation. Personnel records are closed until 2041.
  - General Files, 1938-1999 and undated
    - Adweek meeting, circa 1996 (Box 1)
    - Agency brochure, undated (Box 1)
    - Agency credentials, circa 1990 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Agency factbook, 1996 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Agency letterhead, undated (Box 1)
    - Agency profile, undated, (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - Agency website, 1997 and undated (Box 1)
    - American Advertising Federation, 1995-1996 (Box 1)
    - Awards, 1995-1997 (Box 1)
    - Brochure materials development, undated (Box 1)
    - Marketing Forum, 1996-1999, (1-8 of 16 folders) (Box 2)
    - Marketing Forum, 1996-1999 (continued), (9-16 of 16 folders) (Box 3)
    - Memoranda, 1987-1996, (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Minutes--Warwick & Legler, 1938-1943 (Box 4)
    - Minutes--Warwick & Legler, 1944-1954 (Box 5)
    - Minutes--Warwick & Legler, 1955-1962 (Box 6)
    - Minutes--Warwick & Legler, 1962-1970 (Box 7)
    - Minutes--Warwick & Legler, 1971-1972 (Box 8)
    - Minutes--Warwick Welsh & Miller, 1973-1977 (Box 8)
    - Minutes--Warwick Welsh & Miller, 1978-1980 (Box 9)
    - Minutes, 1988-1990 (Box 9)
    - Print advertising reprints, 1999 and undated (Box 9)
    - Printed material
      - Brandweek, Superbrands, 1996 (Box 9)
      - Just the Facts (agency pamphlet), 1998 (Box 9)
      - Leadership directories, 1997 (Box 9)
      - Parade, 1997 (Box 9)
      - Red Book listing, 1997 (Box 9)
      - What is this? (agency brochure), 1997 (Box 9)
    - Staff
      - Gender survey, 1997 (Box 9)
      - Inside Media, profile of Mike Haggarty, 1991 (Box 9)
      - Photograph of Andy Piccone, undated (Box 9)
      - Stock shareholdings, 1970s (Box 9)
    - Subsidiaries and partners, 1978-1997 and undated
      - Interpartners, 1996-1997 and undated, (4 folders) (Box 10)
      - Lopex Limited/Lopex Group, 1978-1979, (2 folders) (Box 10)
      - Marketing Network/Black Bag Communications, 1995 (Box 10)
  - Legal Files, 1953-1994
    - Agreements and contracts, 1953-1994, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield corporate contract, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Brooke Bond Foods (Red Rose tea), 1978-1981 (Box 11)
    - Burlington Industries/Klopman Mills, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Calvin Cooler/Joseph Victori, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Corporate notaries (Barnes, Fierman), 1984-1990 (Box 11)
    - Coty/Pfizer (Emeraude, Chateau, Stetson), 1981-1987 (Box 11)
    - Costa Cruises, 1981 (Box 11)
    - CPC International, 1977-1991 (Box 11)
    - Crossland Savings, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Food from Britain, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Grolsch, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Harbridge House, 1984 (Box 12)
    - HomEquity, 1986-1987 (Box 12)
    - Jockey International, 1986-1987 (Box 12)
    - Kenvic Associates lease, 1980 (Box 12)
    - Kessler, 1960-1964 (Box 12)
    - King Cola, 1979-1981 (Box 12)
    - Lehn & Fink, 1983-1991 (Box 12)
    - Lopex Limited/Lopex Group, 1978-1979, (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - PAGG, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
    - Polar Trading Company, 1985 (Box 12)
    - Rocco, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Russell Harris Linder (re: Seagrams), 1975-1983 (Box 12)
    - Seagram's Distillers, 1960-1984, (3 folders) (Box 13)
    - Smithsonian Magazine, 1974-1989 (Box 13)
    - Sterling Drug, 1984-1988 (Box 13)
    - Thomas-Koch acquisition, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Warwick Plus, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Western Publishing, 1992-1994, (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Public Relations, 1956-2001 and undated
    - Agency clips, 1991-1993 (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 14)
    - Memoranda, 1991-1997, (4 folders) (Box 14)
    - News Release/Bulletin Board, 1956-1984, (6 folders) (Box 15)
    - Press and media, 1997 and undated (Box 16)
    - Press contact lists, 1994-1995 (Box 16)
    - Press release guide, undated (Box 16)
    - Press releases, 1991-2001, (5 folders) (Box 16)
    - Shady Brook Farms campaign release, undated (Box 16)
  - Research, 1988-1999 and undated
    - Accupol, 1997 (Box 16)
    - Animatics, 1991-1993 (Box 16)
    - ASI Market Research--Sales-Calibrated Copy Testing, 1996 (Box 16)
    - Basic Research--Rough vs. Finished Copy Testing, 1990 (Box 16)
    - Canada: A Country of Distinction (A.C. Nielsen), 1995 (Box 17)
    - Canada Food and Drug Retail (A.C. Nielsen), 1996 (Box 17)
    - Copy testing, 1990-1998, (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Electric shavers, 1996-1997 (Box 17)
    - Fast food, 1995-1997 (Box 17)
    - Find/SVP--VPN articles, 1996-1998 (Box 17)
    - Food and health, 1996 (Box 17)
    - Food articles, 1996 (Box 17)
    - Food trends, 1993-1996, (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Fortune--Saving and Investing in the 90s, 1994 (Box 18)
    - Fortune/Yankelovich--Leveraging Corporate Equity, 1994 (Box 18)
    - Global Business Network Scenario Planning, 1997 (Box 18)
    - Infoscan--Market and Region Profiles, 1993 (Box 18)
    - JWT--Thompson Account Planning, 1996 (Box 18)
    - Marketing Analysts Inc.--Advertising Copy Testing, 1999, (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - Mediawatch--Competitor Spending, 1996 (Box 18)
    - Music, 1988-1996 (Box 18)
    - Photo Marketing Association--Industry Trends Report, 1993-1994 (Box 18)
    - Promo--The In-Store Experience vol. 1, 1994 (Box 19)
    - Questionnaires, 1995 and undated (Box 19)
    - Real-Time Response Survey in New Consumer Product Research (Lynne Kahle), 1993 (Box 19)
    - Russell Marketing Research--Hair Removal Product Name and Package Evaluation Study, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Travel articles, 1996 (Box 19)
    - Used Gold Reference Guide (CNW Marketing/Research), circa 1995 (Box 19)
    - Vehicle models, undated (Box 19)
    - What Makes Effective Advertising Today? (McCollum Spielman Worldwide), undated (Box 19)
    - Wine (Forest Glen), 1998 (Box 19)
    - Yankelovich Monitor, undated (Box 19)
  - Vendors, 1988-2000 and undated
    - Lists of consultants, 1997 (Box 19)
    - AAAA, 1996 (Box 19)
    - Adscope, 1998 (Box 19)
    - Advertising Information Services, 1997 (Box 20)
    - Advertising Partnership, 1996 (Box 20)
    - Alliance International, 1994-1995 (Box 20)
    - Allscope Media, undated (Box 20)
    - Ameritest, 1999 (Box 20)
    - Andrew J. Kelly Associates, 1992 (Box 20)
    - Brand Equities, undated (Box 20)
    - BrandTraq training manual, undated (Box 20)
    - BYG Associates, 1996 (Box 20)
    - Chapman Warwick, undated (Box 20)
    - CLT Research Associates, undated (Box 20)
    - Competitive Media Reporting--Adspender training manual, undated (Box 20)
    - C.Y. Research--Ameritest/AD2, undated (Box 20)
    - Decision Training Systems, 1995 (Box 20)
    - Donovan and Associates, 1996 (Box 20)
    - DRI Advertising Research, undated (Box 20)
    - Dunwoodie, undated (Box 20)
    - EMA--Eric Mower & Associates, undated (Box 20)
    - Executive Forum (HBO), 1997 (Box 20)
    - Find/SVP, 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - Greenfield Online, 1996 (Box 21)
    - Hal Goldberg--Creative Q for Q-Sort Research, undated (Box 21)
    - Harvard Business School reprints (Staples, CompUSA, McDonald's, Burger King, Circuit City), 1995-1996 (Box 21)
    - Interpro, 1999 (Box 21)
    - Issues and Answers, 1999 (Box 21)
    - James E. Arnold and Associates, 1998 (Box 21)
    - J.E. Clucas & Associates, undated (Box 21)
    - JWT Consumer Behavior Department, undated (Box 21)
    - Maritz Marketing Research, 1996 (Box 21)
    - Market Research Associates, 1996 (Box 21)
    - Market Voice, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Media Industry Newsletter, 1995 (Box 21)
    - Metro Market Research Center, undated (Box 21)
    - Namelab, undated (Box 21)
    - Nametag Inc., 1992 (Box 21)
    - Olsten Corp., 1997 (Box 21)
    - Omega Group, undated (Box 21)
    - Partners in Research, 1993 (Box 21)
    - Personal Opinion Inc., undated (Box 21)
    - Philadelphia Focus, undated (Box 21)
    - Pickholz Tweedy, 2000 (Box 21)
    - Plaza Research, undated (Box 21)
    - Portico Research, 1995 (Box 21)
    - Psychologics, undated (Box 21)
    - Reprint Management Services, 1997 (Box 22)
    - Richard Kurtz, 1996 (Box 22)
    - Richard Saunders International, 1993 (Box 22)
    - Sales Marketing Institute, 1998 (Box 22)
    - Select Resources International, 1998 (Box 22)
    - Snap Professional/Mercator Corporation, undated (Box 22)
    - Special Libraries Association, 1996 (Box 22)
    - Strategic Vision, A Value-Centered Model, undated (Box 22)
    - Synectics/Name Session, 1988-1994 (Box 22)
    - The Leslie Agency, 1999 (Box 22)
    - The Marketing Network, 1994 (Box 22)
    - The Mitchell Company, 1999 (Box 22)
    - The Pretesting Company, 1999 (Box 22)
    - Tropical Alliance Communications (Singapore), undated (Box 22)
    - Video Monitoring Services (VMS), undated (Box 22)
    - Video Pitch, 1998 (Box 22)
  - Restricted Materials
    - General Files (closed until 2015) (Box R1)
      - Consultant mailing list, 1998-1999 (Box R1)
      - Effie Awards, 1998-1999, (2 folders) (Box R1)
      - Interpartners, 1999 (Box R1)
      - Marketing Forum, 1998, (3 folders) (Box R1)
      - Red Book renewal, 2000 (Box R1)
      - WBO website, 1998 (Box R1)
    - Personnel-related records (closed until 2041)
      - Employee savings plan, 1980-1989 (Box R1)
      - Quantitative position candidates, 1995 (Box R1)
      - Retirement plan, 1988-1989, (3 folders) (Box R1)
- Account Files, 1973-2001 and undated, (75 boxes)
  - General Files
    - Account planning articles, 1993 (Box AF1)
    - Account Planning Group, 1997 (Box AF1)
    - Account planning presentation, undated, (2 folders) (Box AF1)
    - Brand assessment program, undated (Box AF1)
  - American Mental Health Fund
    - Advertising strategy, 1988 (Box AF1)
    - Campaign strategy review, 1990 (Box AF1)
    - General, 1985-1986 (Box AF1)
    - Printed material, 1984-1985 (Box AF1)
    - Report covering mental illness one-on-one interviews, 1990 (Box AF1)
    - Research proposal--Motivating sufferers and families to seek help for mental illness, 1989 (Box AF1)
    - Robert Wood Johnson's Yankelovich study, 1989 (Box AF1)
  - Archer Services
    - Communications strategy, 1987 (Box AF1)
  - Bausch & Lomb
    - Brand equity review, 1997 (Box AF2)
    - Computer Drops naming, 1997 (Box AF2)
    - Computer Eyes, 1997 (Box AF2)
    - Curèl testing, 1995-1997 (Box AF2)
    - Dry Eye Therapy, 1997 (Box AF2)
    - Eye care project, 1997 (Box AF2)
    - Eye care topline report, 1997 (Box AF2)
    - General, 1996-1997 (Box AF2)
    - Moisture Drops, 1996 (Box AF2)
    - Moisture Drops weight test, 1996 (Box AF2)
    - Moisture Eyes/Computer Eyes, 1997 (Box AF2)
    - Opcon-A, 1997 (Box AF2)
    - Planning, undated (Box AF2)
    - Presentation, 1997 (Box AF2)
    - Qualitative study for eye care products, 1997 (Box AF3)
  - Benjamin Moore
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box AF3)
    - Creative research, 1989 (Box AF3)
    - Creative strategy, 1991 (Box AF3)
    - One-on-one interviews, 1989 (Box AF3)
  - Burke Rehabilitation Hospital
    - Printed material, 1997 (Box AF3)
  - Crafted with Pride (Made in the U.S.A.)
    - AAMA directory, 1994 (Box AF3)
    - Account status report, 1991-1992 (Box AF3)
    - Advertising awareness, 1993 (Box AF3)
    - Advertising (Box AF3)
    - General, 1990-1991 (Box AF3)
    - Print/radio, 1991-1992 (Box AF3)
    - Radio, 1994 (Box AF3)
    - Scheduling/testing, 1991-1992 (Box AF3)
    - Television, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box AF4)
    - Trade, 1990-1992 (Box AF4)
    - Billing, 1994 (Box AF4)
    - Brand review, 1987-1991 (Box AF4)
    - Budget, 1990-1994, (1-3 of 5 folders) (Box AF4)
    - Budget, 1990-1994, (4-5 of 5 folders) (Box AF5)
    - Call reports, 1990-1991 (Box AF5)
    - Case study (Harvard Business School), 1987 (Box AF5)
    - Commercial list, undated (Box AF5)
    - Competitive, 1990-1993, (2 folders) (Box AF5)
    - Copy presentation, 1990 (Box AF5)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box AF5)
    - Correspondence--Bobbin letter, 1994 (Box AF5)
    - Correspondence--Letter to Robert Reich, 1995 (Box AF5)
    - Creative--Kansas City, Jones Store, 1993 (Box AF5)
    - Creative strategy, 1994 (Box AF5)
    - DuPont request, 1994 (Box AF6)
    - General, 1992-1993, (2 folders) (Box AF6)
    - Industry analysis, 1994 (Box AF6)
    - Industry information, 1994-1995, (3 folders) (Box AF6)
    - Information file--Apparel industry, 1994 (Box AF6)
    - Information file--ATM1, 1994 (Box AF6)
    - Information file--GATT/NAFTA articles, 1994 (Box AF6)
    - Information file--General, 1993-1994, (1 of 5 folders) (Box AF6)
    - Information file--General, 1993-1994, (2-5 of 5 folders) (Box AF7)
    - Information file--World Trade Organization, 1994 (Box AF7)
    - Legal (Box AF7)
    - General, 1990-1993 (Box AF7)
    - Substantiation, 1990-1993, (1-3 of 6 folders) (Box AF7)
    - Substantiation, 1990-1993, (4-6 of 6 folders) (Box AF8)
    - Logos and designs, undated (Box AF8)
    - Market reports, 1989-1992, (1-5 of 7 folders) (Box AF8)
    - Market reports, 1989-1992, (6-7 of 7 folders) (Box AF9)
    - Marketing (Box AF9)
    - General, 1990-1993, (2 folders) (Box AF9)
    - International, 1991 (Box AF9)
    - Plans/recommendations, 1990-1992, (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box AF9)
    - Plans/recommendations, 1990-1992, (3 of 3 folders) (Box AF10)
    - Promotions, 1990-1992, (7 folders) (Box AF10)
    - Public relations, 1991 (Box AF10)
    - Test market, 1991 (Box AF10)
    - Youth, 1986-1990, (2 folders) (Box AF10)
    - Marketing Committee, 1990-1991, (5 folders) (Box AF11)
    - Marketing meetings, 1990-1991, (3 folders) (Box AF11)
    - Media (Box AF11)
    - General, 1989-1994, (1-3 of 4 folders) (Box AF11)
    - General, 1989-1994, (4 of 4 folders) (Box AF12)
    - Budgets, 1990-1994 (Box AF12)
    - Buying/implementation, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box AF12)
    - Estimates, 1994 (Box AF12)
    - Memoranda, 1993-1994 (Box AF12)
    - Planning, 1989-1992 (Box AF12)
    - Post analysis, 1990-1992 (Box AF12)
    - Print, 1990-1992 (Box AF13)
    - Radio, 1991-1993 (Box AF13)
    - Scheduling, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box AF13)
    - Television, 1990-1993, (3 folders) (Box AF13)
    - Trade print, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box AF13)
    - Traffic, 1991-1992 (Box AF14)
    - Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box AF14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992-1993, (2 folders) (Box AF14)
    - Miss America (Box AF14)
    - General, 1988-1992, (5 folders) (Box AF14)
    - Kenner tie-in, undated (Box AF15)
    - Promotions, 1989-1992, (1-8 of 10 folders) (Box AF15)
    - Promotions, 1989-1992, (9-10 of 10 folders) (Box AF16)
    - NRF Conference, 1993, (2 folders) (Box AF16)
    - Presentation, 1990 (Box AF16)
    - Press conference, 1991 (Box AF16)
    - Printed material (Box AF16)
    - Body Shop animal testing brochures, 1994 (Box AF16)
    - Brochure, undated (Box AF16)
    - Buy Australian, 1994 (Box AF16)
    - Feature in Apparel News, 1993 (Box AF16)
    - God's Love We Deliver, undated (Box AF16)
    - Update Newsletter, 1994 (Box AF16)
    - Product name/logo, 1990-1992 (Box AF16)
    - Production, 1990-1994, (3 folders) (Box AF16)
    - Public relations, 1991-1993, (1-10 of 12 folders) (Box AF17)
    - Public relations, 1991-1993, (11-12 of 12 folders) (Box AF18)
    - Quick response, 1990-1993, (2 folders) (Box AF18)
    - Research (Box AF18)
    - General, 1988-1993, (1-5 of 13 folders) (Box AF18)
    - General, 1988-1993, (6-10 of 13 folders) (Box AF19)
    - Apparel pricing, 1994 (Box AF19)
    - Focus groups, 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box AF20)
    - IMRA consumer survey, 1994 (Box AF20)
    - Insurance industry advocacy campaigns, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box AF20)
    - One-on-one interviews, 1994 (Box AF20)
    - Phase I-II, 1994, (2 folders) (Box AF20)
    - Post buy analysis, 1994 (Box AF20)
    - Proposal, 1994, (2 folders) (Box AF20)
    - Qualitative, 1990-1991, (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box AF20)
    - Qualitative, 1990-1991, (3 of 3 folders) (Box AF21)
    - Reasons to buy, 1993 (Box AF21)
    - Tracking, 1989-1990, (8 folders) (Box AF21)
    - Tracking, 1990-1992, (10 folders) (Box AF22)
    - Tracking, 1992-1993, (9 folders) (Box AF23)
    - Tracking, 1993-1994, (10 folders) (Box AF24)
    - Tracking, 1994, (2 folders) (Box AF25)
    - Visa recall study, 1994 (Box AF25)
    - Retail, 1989-1993, (2 folders) (Box AF25)
    - Rowland Company, 1991 (Box AF25)
    - Status report, 1992 (Box AF25)
    - Steering Committee, 1990-1991, (1 of 5 folders) (Box AF25)
    - Steering Committee, 1990-1991, (2-5 of 5 folders) (Box AF26)
    - Strategy, 1990 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF26)
    - Talent holding fees, 1994-1995 (Box AF26)
    - Think tank meeting, 1991 (Box AF26)
    - Traffic, 1993-1994 (Box AF26)
  - Dawson Home Fashions
    - Accessories research, 1990 (Box AF27)
    - Bath accessories research, 1990-1992 (Box AF27)
    - Collage brand meeting, 1993 (Box AF27)
    - Shower curtain market study, 1992 (Box AF27)
  - Driver's Mart
    - Advertising manual, undated, (2 folders) (Box AF27)
    - General, 1996-1997, (2 folders) (Box AF27)
    - New automotive economics, 1997 (Box AF27)
    - Presentation, undated (Box AF28)
    - Printed advertising, undated (Box AF28)
    - Reports, 1996 (Box AF28)
    - Strategy, 1996 (Box AF29)
  - East Coast Energy Council (ECEC)
    - General, 1995 (Box AF29)
    - Exploratory study, 1997 (Box AF29)
    - Fall 1998 planning, 1998 (Box AF29)
    - Oil heat advertising exploratory, 1996 (Box AF29)
    - Oil Heat Institute homeowner study, 1998 (Box AF29)
    - Planning meeting, 1997 (Box AF29)
    - Qualitative (Box AF29)
    - General, 1994-1997, (3 folders) (Box AF29)
    - Oil heat, 1996-1997 (Box AF29)
    - Radio scripts, 1998 (Box AF29)
    - Research, 1994-1997 (Box AF29)
    - Spring 1995 planning, 1994 (Box AF29)
    - Turner tracking study, 1993-1999, (6 folders) (Box AF30)
  - Fruit of the Loom
    - General, 1997 (Box AF30)
    - Brand research presentation, 1992 (Box AF30)
    - Business Facts, 1992 (Box AF31)
    - BVD (Box AF31)